So when people say things to me like, I don't want to vote for the lesser of two evils,
I'm tired of that. What I want you to understand is something like this.
This country, America, is a continual process of digging its way out of the hellhole that it was
born from. It is a process of strategy, it is a process of forward and backward movement. We know
that change is not linear. It is a process of reform, it is a process of revolution.
What that requires is constant efforts toward the forward. Sometimes that requires making
strategic decisions that simply just allow for more time for rallying, for radicalism,
for rebellion, for learning, for educating. So when you see folks saying vote for Biden,
when you see folks saying simply just vote Democrat, what many of us are saying is there
is an extreme that is happening on the right. And even though there is a moderate happening in the
Democrats and there is a progressive side, it is giving more time for an environment where that
radicalism can grow without the extremism suppressing it. That is strategy. And you and your personal
decisions about, I don't want to vote for the lesser of two evils are in the way. Move around
and actually move in because we need everybody. Right Jedi.